hope.dating 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy

Hope is committed to ensuring your personal information is protected. This privacy policy has been created to demonstrate our commitment in safeguarding your personal information and informing you about ways in which your information is handled.

Hope reserves the rights to change the privacy policy at any time and users shall be notified about any such changes. Each time you visit this site or provide information, you're accepting these policies. In case you do not agree with the policies mentioned in this contract, you're advised not to register with this site and use any of the services.

**IP Address**

Each time you visit this site, we collect your IP address and well as details of the web page that directed you to this site. This information plays a critical role in optimizing the website and diagnosing any problems. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are saved on your computer for keeping a record of some websites. These cookies are also employed to deliver content, specific to your requirements and interests. They can be used to save your password, financial and personal information, so you don’t have to enter it every time you visit the website. If you wish to disable cookies, simply visit your browser settings and check the relevant option.

**Information Collected from Users**

Hope collects personal information from its users. This is done to operate the site as well as to occasionally display advertisements. We shall also collect personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, residential address and phone number, among others. Kindly note this information shall not be publicly visible. In addition, your financial information such as credit card numbers and passwords shall also be collected.

We may also include certain demographical information, which may include but is not limited to gender, zip code, or birth date. We will not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from people under the age of 18 years, as this site requires users to be 18 years or older.

**How do we use personal information?**

Your personal information as well as other personally identifiable information shall be used to efficiently operate this site and communicate with you. This type of communication is commonly referred to as “Operational Communication”. To operate this site, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives and service providers so that they can lend support as well as customer relationship management services.

**Accessing and Updating your email preferences, personal information and public information**

We give users the opportunity to modify personal information or demographic data at anytime. Please note that changes made to public information may take several hours to reflect on the website. Changing or deleting information shall only change or delete information in our database. 

These changes or deletions shall not change or delete information that we’ve already forwarded to our partners or agents.
